<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-08-20T14:37:20+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">HOME</title><subtitle>Your premier destination for unforgettable party events and celebrations!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Announcing Afrobeat Night – Patchania Events</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/events/announcement/2025/08/20/Coming-event.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Announcing Afrobeat Night – Patchania Events" /><published>2025-08-20T08:23:38+02:00</published><updated>2025-08-20T08:23:38+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/events/announcement/2025/08/20/Coming-event</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/events/announcement/2025/08/20/Coming-event.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="-get-ready-for-afrobeat-night---patchania-events-">🎉 Get Ready for Afrobeat Night! - Patchania Events 🎉</h1>

<p>Patchania Events is delighted to present <strong>Afrobeat Night</strong>, an exclusive celebration of vibrant music, energetic dancing, and the unmistakable spirit of Afrobeat. Join us for an unforgettable evening designed to bring together enthusiasts and newcomers alike.</p>

<hr />

<h2 id="event-details">Event Details</h2>

<table>
  <thead>
    <tr>
      <th style="text-align: center"><strong>Date</strong></th>
      <th style="text-align: center"><strong>Time</strong></th>
      <th style="text-align: center"><strong>Venue</strong></th>
    </tr>
  </thead>
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <td style="text-align: center">November 8, 2025</td>
      <td style="text-align: center">10:00 PM – Late</td>
      <td style="text-align: center">Patchania Events Hall</td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>

<hr />

<h2 id="what-to-expect">What to Expect</h2>

<ul>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Live Afrobeat Performances</strong><br />
  Experience the best of Afrobeat with renowned artists and top DJs.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><strong>All-Night Dance Floor</strong><br />
  Enjoy a lively atmosphere and dance the night away.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Premium Drinks &amp; Refreshments</strong><br />
  Savor a selection of delicious beverages throughout the event.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p><strong>Exclusive Surprises &amp; Giveaways</strong><br />
  Participate in special activities and win exciting prizes.</p>
  </li>
</ul>

<hr />

<h2 id="rsvp--contact">RSVP &amp; Contact</h2>

<p>Mark your calendar and invite your friends for an evening of music, connection, and celebration.<br />
For inquiries or to RSVP, connect with us on <a href="https://instagram.com/patchaniaevents">Instagram</a>.</p>

<hr />

<p>We look forward to welcoming you to Afrobeat Night!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="events" /><category term="announcement" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Get Ready for Afrobeat Night! - Patchania Events 🎉 Patchania Events is delighted to present Afrobeat Night, an exclusive celebration of vibrant music, energetic dancing, and the unmistakable spirit of Afrobeat. Join us for an unforgettable evening designed to bring together enthusiasts and newcomers alike. Event Details Date Time Venue November 8, 2025 10:00 PM – Late Patchania Events Hall What to Expect Live Afrobeat Performances Experience the best of Afrobeat with renowned artists and top DJs. All-Night Dance Floor Enjoy a lively atmosphere and dance the night away. Premium Drinks &amp; Refreshments Savor a selection of delicious beverages throughout the event. Exclusive Surprises &amp; Giveaways Participate in special activities and win exciting prizes. RSVP &amp; Contact Mark your calendar and invite your friends for an evening of music, connection, and celebration. For inquiries or to RSVP, connect with us on Instagram. We look forward to welcoming you to Afrobeat Night!]]></summary></entry></feed>